data =
    '[{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "What is the first phase of|Software Testing Life Cycle(STLC)?", "answer" : "Requirement Analysis"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "Which type of software testing can be done|without programming knowledge? ", "answer" : "Manual Testing"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "What is followed on first stage in automation testing? ", "answer" : "Test Tool Selection"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "What acceptance test is based on?", "answer" : "User Requirements"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "Which testing approach known as “structural testing”?", "answer" : "White Box Testing"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "What are the two main categories of black box testing?", "answer" : "Functional, Non-functional"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "In which SDLC methodology it is easy to change project requirements?", "answer" : "Agile"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "V-model is a model of ---? ", "answer" : "SDLC"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "What is the 3rd step of STLC?", "answer" : "Environment Setup"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "What are the software mistakes that occurs|during in the coding phase?", "answer" : "Bugs"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "Which testing strategy helps developers to know if the individual unit of the code is working properly?", "answer" : "Unit Testing"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "At what stage of STLC developers prepare hardware|and software requirement list?", "answer" : "Test Environment Setup"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "In which sequential Software Development Life Cycle(SDLC) model testing|phase starts only after implementation of the system is done?", "answer" : "Waterfall Model"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "Which type of testing’s purpose is to test the|reading speed of the software system?", "answer" : "Non-functional Testing"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "At which stage of STLC, requirements are clarified with stakeholders?", "answer" : "Requirement Analysis"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "A testing technique to test the application with|partial knowledge of the internal workings.", "answer" : "Grey Box Testing"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "A level of testing mainly used to test the data|flow from one module to other module.", "answer" : "Integration Testing"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "A type of software testing method where developers test the system performance|under certain load conditions over an extensive period.", "answer" : "Endurance Testing"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "Which technique is applied for usability testing?", "answer" : "Black Box Testing"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "Which testing type offers better application with less effort?", "answer" : "Automation testing"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "A type of software testing method which is used to|check the application without executing the code.", "answer" : "Static Testing"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "A black box testing technique that uses a systematic approach where the|various input combinations and their following system behaviour are captured in a tabular form.", "answer" : "Decision Table Testing"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "A testing technique in which there is no method for identifying the error and it is|based on the experience of the test analyst, where the developer uses their experience to guess the problematic areas of the software.", "answer" : "Error Guessing Technique"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "A type of software testing that is intended to discover the weaknesses,|flaws of a software application as well as protect data.", "answer" : "Security Testing"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "In this type of software testing, users and customers determine|whether the software is conforming specified requirements or not.", "answer" : "Acceptance Testing"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "This type of software tool is used to test the user interface of the|application and loopholes can be identified quickly with using this tool rather than testing manually.", "answer" : "GUI Testing Tool"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "A type of non-functional testing tool that enables to compare|a web application in the various web browser platforms.", "answer" : "Cross-browser Testing Tool"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "A type of testing tool which helps the programmers to|improve their code. Thus, it reduces the time spent on coding.", "answer" : "Unit Testing Tool"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "This type of testing tool is used to check the software|application’s load, stability and scalability.", "answer" : "Performance Testing Tool"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "A white box testing type where developers insert errors purposely into the program to|verify whether the existing test case can detect the error or not.", "answer" : "Mutation Testing"}]';